hey everybody i have some great news for
you all i'm starting a monthly podcast
for advanced listening practice that
will help you reach a higher level of
listening comprehension in english this
podcast will be available for listening
time family members on the fifth day of
every month each advanced episode will
be just like my normal listening time
podcast episodes but i'll be speaking at
normal speed it'll be much faster and
more challenging than my normal episodes
but don't worry you'll have the
transcript available for each episode if
you enjoy the listening time podcast and
you can already understand most of what
i say in each episode then you'll
definitely want to use my advanced
podcast to understand fast native
english if you want to finally reach an
advanced level of listening
comprehension then become a listening
time family member today for just four
dollars per month at patreon.com
listening time in addition to the
advanced podcast listening time family
members also receive an extra podcast
episode a sound training video a
listening practice seminar and an
additional listening or pronunciation
seminar every month just click on the
link below in the description box and
become a listening time family member
today